Guide to the Stephen M. Cabrinety Collection in the History of Microcomputing, ca. 1975-1995
Department of Special Collections
- Software, Series 1
  - Games, Subseries 1.4
    - JMH Software of Minnesota, Inc. Atari Custom Disk Vowel O, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 151)
    - JMH Software of Minnesota, Inc. Atari Custom Disk Vowel U, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 151)
    - John Besnard Arcade Boot Camp, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 43)
    - John Konopa Starship Duel, 1980, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 131)
    - Joker Software Aussie Joker Poker, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 109)
    - Joker Software Aussie Joker Poker, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 113)
    - Jor-And Secret Agent: Mission One, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 116)
    - JV Software, Inc. Action Quest, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 127)
    - JV Software, Inc. Journey to the Planets, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 130)
    - JVC Musical Industries, Inc. Ghool Patrol, 1994, 1 computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 204)
    - JVC Musical Industries, Inc. Super Star Wars, 1991, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 9)
    - K.-H. Lemaire und Günther Krämer im Vertreib der Rono GMBH Köln Galaxy Fight: The Incredible Space Flight, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 198)
    - K-Byte K-DOS Handbook, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 131)
    - K-Tek Video Software Stomp Ground, 1983, computer cassetteCommodore 64/128 (Box 183)
    - KAB Software Neutral Corners, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - Kaneco Co., Ltd. DJ Boy, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Kaneko USA, Ltd. Wild, Wild Quest with Chester Cheetah, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Kastel Technology Trivia Savant: the ultimate informational challenge, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 37)
    - Kemco America, Inc. Dr. Franken, 1992, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Kemco America, Inc. Ka-Blooey, 1992, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 9)
    - Kemco America, Inc. Phalanx, 1991, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 9)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Action Adventures (Climber, G*Man, Diamond Dig), 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 137)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Arcade Bonanza, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 137)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Arcade Bonanza [Frog, Pac-em, Red Alert, Tank!], 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 172)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Arcade Games, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 43)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Arcade II, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 169)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Astronomy Pak, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Black Monday, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 60)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Circus Circus, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 176)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Club Casino, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 107)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Convoy, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 161)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Fun in Learning, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 177)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Gambler, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 145)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Kong-Quest, 1987, computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 16)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Land your dream job: the Resume Writer, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 160)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. On The Run, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Saboteur II, 1989, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 170)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Seahunt, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 107)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Sports Spectacular, 1987, computer disk; 3 ½ in. MS-DOS (Box 18)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Sports Spectacular, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 137)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Sports Spectacular (Baseball, Football, Hockey), 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 22)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Stock Manager, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Strategy Games [Ruler, Killer Bees, Engineer, Sabotage, Vampire], 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 172)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Strategy Simulations, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 135)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Swords and sorcery, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 169)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Torpedos Away, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 105)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Viper Patrol, 1987, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 103)
    - Keypunch Software, Inc. Wargames (battle buggy, space bomber, air raid, panzer), 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 23)
    - Kinetica Software U.S. Gold: The Gold of the Aztecs, 1991, computer disk; 3 ½ in. MS-DOS (Box 18)
    - Koala Technologies Corporation Instant Programmer's Guide, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 141)
    - KoalaWare Coloring Series II: Crystal Flowers and Snowflakes, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 141)
    - KOEI Corporation Nobunaga's Ambition, 1990, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Konami Blades of Steel, 1990, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Commodore (Box 194)
    - Konami Gradius, 1986, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 204)
    - Konami J.R.R. Tolkien's Riders of Rohan, 1991, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 159)
    - Konami, Inc. Action City Ping Pong, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 187)
    - Konami, Inc. Action City Ping Pong, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 190)
    - Konami, Inc. Adventures of Yogi Bear, 1991, 1 computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 202)
    - Konami, Inc. Axelay, 1992, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 8)
    - Konami, Inc. Batman Returns Version, 1992, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 10)
    - Konami, Inc. Batman Returns, 1991, 1 computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 202)
    - Konami, Inc. Blades of Steel, 1990, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. MS-DOS (Box 3)
    - Konami, Inc. Contra (one of the all-time classic games of the late 80s), 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. MS-DOS (Box 4)
    - Konami, Inc. Double Dribble: The Playoff Edition, 1994, computer cartridgeSEGA Genesis (Box 6)
    - Konami, Inc. Gradius: Interstellar Assault, 1992, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Konami, Inc. Gradius: Interstellar Assault, 1992, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 199)
    - Konami, Inc. King's Quest V, 1992, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 10)
    - Konami, Inc. Konami presents Tiny Toon adventures Wacky Sports Challenge, 1994, 1 computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 204)
    - Konami, Inc. Lethal Enforcers II: Gun Fighters, 1994, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.SEGA CD (Box 23)
    - Konami, Inc. NFL Videopro Football, 1992, computer disk; 3 ½ in. MS-DOS (Box 17)
    - Konami, Inc. Predator 2 (he's in town with a few days to kill...), 1991, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. MS-DOS (Box 4)
    - Konami, Inc. Rush'n Attack, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. MS-DOS (Box 4)
    - Konami, Inc. Sparkster, 1994, 1 computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 206)
    - Konami, Inc. Sunset Riders, 1992, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Konami, Inc. Sunsetriders, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 204)
    - Konami Inc Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, 1990, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 131)
    - Konami, Inc. Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Fall of the Foot Clan, 1991, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Konami, Inc. Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II: Back from the Sewers, 1991, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Konami, Inc. Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles III: Radical Rescue Game Boy game pak, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 8)
    - Konami, Inc. Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV: Turtles in Time, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 9)
    - Konami, Inc. The CastleVania Adventure, 1989, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Konami, Inc. Tiny Toon Adventures 2: Trouble in Wackyland, 1993, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 10)
    - Konami, Inc. Tiny Toon Adventures: Buster Busts Loose!, 1991, 1 computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 202)
    - Konami, Inc. Top Gun: The Second Mission, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - Konami, Inc. Track and Field, 1992, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Konami Inc Track & Field, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 57)
    - Konami, Inc. Where in the world is Carmen Sandiego?, 1991, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 11)
    - Konami, Inc. Yie Ar Kung-Fu 2, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Konami, Inc. Zen: Intergalactic Ninja, 1991, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 11)
    - Konami, Inc. Zombies ate my neighbors, 1993, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 9)
    - Konami Industries, Inc. Gyrus, 1984, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - Konami Industry, Co. Track & Field, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 143)
    - Konami Industry Co., Ltd. Super Cobra, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 134)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Batman: The Animated Series, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 206)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Castlevania: Bloodlines, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Castlevania II: Belmon's Revenge, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 206)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Contra: Hard Corps, 1994, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Kid Dracula, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 206)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Hyper Stone Heist, 1991, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Tournament Fighters, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 206)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles Tournament Fighters, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Tiny Toon Adventures 2: Montana's Movie Madness, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 206)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Tiny Toon Adventures: Buster's Hidden Treasure, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Tutankham, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - Konami USA, Inc. Zen Intergalactic Ninja, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 206)
    - Kraker Jax, Inc. The Shotgun, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 201)
    - Krentek Software Rome and the Barbarians, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 128)
    - Krisalis Software, Ltd. Botics, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 96)
    - Krisalis Software, Ltd. Mad Professor Mariarti, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 104)
    - Krisalis Software, Ltd. Rogue Trooper, 1990, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 76)
    - Krisalis Software, Ltd. Rogue Trooper, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 100)
    - Krisalis Software, Ltd. Rogue Trooper, n.d., computer cartridgeAtari (Box 145)
    - L & S Computerware, Inc. Acey - Deucy, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 43)
    - L & S Computerware, Inc. Acey - Deucy, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 152)
    - L & S Computerware, Inc. Acey-Deucy, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 134)
    - Lance Haffner Games Basketball: The PRO game, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 102)
    - Lance Haffner Games Final Four College Basketball, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 102)
    - Lance Haffner Games Final Four College Basketball, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Landmark Entertainment Group Captain Power and the Soldiers of the Future, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Leading Technology, Inc. Collector Series Software: Entertainment [Hare Raising Havoc.--John Madden Football.--Battlechess II: Chinese Chess.--Links.--Golden Axe.--Stunt Driver.], n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 14)
    - Learning Technologies Alpine Tram Ride, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 194)
    - Learning Technologies Monkey Business, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 173)
    - Learning Technologies Monkey Business, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 194)
    - Lee Trevino's Fighting Golf Mendel Palace, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 205)
    - Lee Trevino's Fighting Golf SNK Corporation of America, 1988, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 205)
    - Legend Entertainment Company Sorcerer's Appliance, 1991, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 161)
    - Leisure Genius A Question of Scruples: The Computer Edition, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 107)
    - Leisure Genius Monty Plays Scrabble, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 20)
    - Leisure Genius Monty Plays Scrabble, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 95)
    - Leisure Genius Monty plays Scrabble, 1988, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 180)
    - Leisure Genius Monty plays Scrabble, 1988, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 198)
    - Level-10, a division of Dakin5 Corp. Neutrons: Strategic Situations, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 106)
    - Lightspeed Software The Observatory, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 125)
    - Linel Dugger starring Herbie Stone, 1988, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 136)
    - LJK Computer Based Software Enterprises Letter Perfect word processing for the Apple II and II+, version 4.0, 1981, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 119)
    - LJN Toys, Ltd. Gotcha!, 1985, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 205)
    - LJN Toys, Ltd. Karate Kid: Master the Martial Arts!, 1987, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 205)
    - LJN Toys, Ltd. Pictionary: The Game of Video Quick Draw, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 10)
    - LJN Toys, Ltd. T2 Terminator 2 Judgement day, 1993, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 9)
    - LJN Toys, Ltd. T2: Terminator 2: Judgement Day, 1993, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 10)
    - LJN Toys, Ltd. WWF Superstars, 1991, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 206)
    - LJN Toys, Ltd. WWF WrestleMania Steel Cage Challenge, 1992, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 11)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software Android Invasion, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 118)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software Chess Champion, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 118)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software Classic Games: Backgammon & Checkers, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 118)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software Fore!: Golfing Simulator, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 118)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software Fore!: Golfing Simulator, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 123)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software Galactic Encounters, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 118)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software Golf!, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 123)
    - Load N Go Software Maze Madness: Labyrinth, Jump, Rat Run, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 187)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software Passport to London, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 112)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software Passport to Paris, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 123)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software Space Adventure, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 118)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software The Adventurer No. 1 Beginner's Cave, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 118)
    - Load 'n' Go! Software Wall Street: A Stock Market Simulator, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 169)
    - Logical Design Works, Inc. California Dreams Vegas Gambler, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 143)
    - Logical Design Works, Inc. Vegas Crap, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 150)
    - Logotron Entertainment Archipelagos, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 98)
    - Logotron Entertainment Archipelagos, 1990, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 131)
    - Logotron Entertainment Bad Company, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 99)
    - Logotron Entertainment Bad Company, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 129)
    - Logotron Entertainment Eye of Horus, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 99)
    - Logotron Entertainment Quadralien, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 96)
    - Logotron Entertainment Star-blaze, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 129)
    - Logotron Entertainment Star-Blaze [Star Blaze; Starblaze], n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 98)
    - Logotron Entertainment StarRay, 1990, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 131)
    - London Software Hot Lips, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 127)
    - London Software Space Ace, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Loriciel Tennis Cup, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 138)
    - Lucas Arts Star Wars: TIE Fighter game, 1994, computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 173)
    - LucasArts, Inc. Maniac Mansion: Day of the Tentacle, Windows (Box 1)
    - LucasArts, Inc. Star Wars Rebel Assault, 1993, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Macintosh (Box 5)
    - Lucasfilm Games Indy, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 163)
    - Lucasfilm Games Indy: Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Amiga (Box 130)
    - Lucasfilm Games Maniac Mansion, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 195)
    - Lucasfilm Games PHM Pegasus: Patrol Hydrofoil Missile Craft Simulation, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 114)
    - Lucasfilm Games Star Wars Jedi Arena, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeColecoVision & ADAM (Box 213)
    - Lucasfilm Games Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - Lucasfilm Games Zak McKracken and the Alien Mindbenders, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 188)
    - Luna Software, Inc. Demo disk, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 199)
    - Luna Software, Inc. Demo Disk, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - Luna Software, Inc. Galactic Crossfire, n.d., 1 computer cartridgeCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - Luna Software, Inc. Hyper-Hen, n.d., 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 212)
    - Luna Software, Inc. Luna Game Graphics Editor, n.d., 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 210)
    - Luna Software, Inc. Pedestrian, 1981, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - M.I. Motocross, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - Mach One Software America's Best 25 Entertainment Hits!, 1991, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 157)
    - Mach One Software America's Best 25 Finance Programs, 1991, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 157)
    - Magic Bytes Blue Angel 69, 1989, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 129)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Alien Invaders, 1980, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Alien Invaders-Plus!, 1980, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Blackjack!, 1978, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Blockout! Breakdown!, 1980, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Cosmic Conflict, 1978, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Freedom Fighters, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Invaders from Hyperspace!, 1979, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company K.C. Munchkin!, 1981, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Odyssey 2: Alpine Skiing!, 1979, 1 computer cartridgeUnknown (Box 95)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Odyssey 2: Baseball!, 1978, 1 computer cartridgeUnknown (Box 95)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Odyssey 2: Blackjack!, 1978, 1 computer cartridgeUnknown (Box 95)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Odyssey 2: Computer Golf!, 1978, 1 computer cartridgeUnknown (Box 95)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Odyssey 2: Computer Intro!, 1979, 1 computer cartridgeUnknown (Box 95)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Odyssey 2: Cosmic Conflict!, 1978, 1 computer cartridgeUnknown (Box 95)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Odyssey 2: Dynasty! and Directional Dynasty!, 1979, 1 computer cartridgeUnknown (Box 95)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Odyssey 2: Football!, 1978, 1 computer cartridgeUnknown (Box 95)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Odyssey 2: Invaders from Hyperspace!, 1979, 1 computer cartridgeUnknown (Box 95)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Odyssey 2: K. C. Munchkin!, 1981, 1 computer cartridgeUnknown (Box 95)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Speedway/ Spin-Out!/ Crypto-Logic, 1978, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Speedway/ Spin-Out!/ Crypto-Logic, 1978, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Sub Chase!, 1978, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company Super Video Arcade Soccer, 1979, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company UFO!, 1980, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnavox Consumer Electronics Company War Room, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeOdyssey 2 by Magnavox (Box 218)
    - Magnetic Images Co. Clip Art, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 154)
    - Magnetic Images Co. Clip Art!, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 154)
    - Magnetic Images Co. Gold of the Realm, 1988, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 41)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Adventure Games, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 113)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Casino Cards, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 113)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Castle Wolfenstein, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 170)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Cribbage/ Bridge Entertainment, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 158)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Familiar Favorites V: Oil's Well, Sammy Lightfoot, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 121)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Flight Landing Simulator, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 85)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Super Hangman, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 90)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Super-Text Word Processor, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 90)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Superman: the strategy game, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 90)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Sword Thrust 1, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 121)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Sword Thrust 4 & 5, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 57)
    - Main Street Publishing, Inc. Trivia, Trivia, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 121)
    - Marcel Programming Cyborg Warrior, 1990, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 147)
    - Mark C. Sumner Pizza!, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Mark of the Unicorn, Inc. Hex, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 135)
    - Martian Software Star Command, 1983, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 39)
    - Master Control Software, Inc. Pharaoh's Pyramid demo, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 155)
    - Master Designer Software S.D.I.: a cinemaware interactive movie, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 128)
    - Master Designer Software S.D.I.: a cinemaware interactive movie, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 198)
    - Master Designer Software, Inc. Defender of the Crown, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 45)